Fried, John H. E.; Papers ger014
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- General correspondence, 1938-1990; 7; 319 file folders
  - Meerloo, Joost, 1967 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Melville, Arthur (DC Nine Defense Committee), 1970 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Mendlovitz, Saul H., 1967-1990 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Mercieca, Charles, 1984 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Merkelbach, Helga, 1977 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Merritt, Richard L., 1977-1983 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Métall, Rudolf A., 1963 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Meyers, William (Fund for New Priorities), 1971; 1974 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Mill, Edward W., 1962-1964 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Montgomery, John D., 1957-1962 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Moral, Antonio Marti, 1985 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Morgenthau, Hans, 1967; 1970 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Morse, Wayne (Senator), 1966 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Mosely, Philip (Council on Foreign Relations), 1956-1960 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Mouton, Jonk & Doreen, 1950-1953 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1985-1987 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Muller, Robert, 1985 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Murphy, Gardner, 1943 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Muskie, Edmund S., 1973; 1976 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Myint-U, Tyn (Pacem in Terris Institute), 1969 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Myrdal, K. Gunnar, 1939 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 18)
  - N, O - miscellaneous correspondence, Undated (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Namier, Lewis, 1953 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Nanda, Ved, 1980-1984 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Nawaz, Mahomet (UNITAR), 1968 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Neu, Moritz, 1953-1954 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Neumann, Sigmund, 1961 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Nevins, Allan, 1948-1960 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Neyer, Joseph, 1982 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Nickl, Hans Paul, 1964 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1970 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Noona, Rosemary, 1989 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Nordman, Joë, 1971-1988 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Nowotny, Thomas, 1980 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Noyes, Pierre, 1970 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 24)
  - O'Brien, William V., 1969-1980 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Oeser, Edith, 1983-1989 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Onyeledo, Godwins-Collins, 1974-1975 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Owen, Joseph W., 1955 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 26)
  - P, Q - miscellaneous correspondence, Undated (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Paech, Norman, 1981-1990 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Paige, Glenn D., 1978; 1985 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Paldy, Lester G., 1982 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Paqué, Ruprecht, 1983 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Parolla & Parolla, 1973-1975 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Parsekian, Ned J., 1987 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Partan, Daniel G., 1972-1974 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Paust, Jordan, 1977 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Pawel, Ernst, 1977 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Perrin, John Clyde, 1969-1970 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Pick, Robert, 1960 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Piel, Eleanor Jackson, 1985 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Pilichowski, Czeslaw, 1976; 1979 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Pitkin, Walter, 1954 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Poltorak, Arcadi N., 1971-1976 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Popkin, Richard H., 1975 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Poppe, Eberhard, 1980-1987 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Porter, Ernest P., 1972 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Porter, Gareth, 1975 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Potter, Pitman, 1943-1956 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Potter, Russell, 1952-1954 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Preminger, Otto, 1962 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Pribram, Karl, 1938-1939 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Proxmire, William (Senator), 1972 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Quigley, John, 1977-1980 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 35)
  - R - miscellaneous correspondence, Undated (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Raab, Ira J., 1977 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor (Louis M. Rabinowitz Foundation, Inc), 1967-1985 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Rangel, Charles B., 1990 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Rapoport, Anatol, 1967 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Raskin, Marcus G., 1974-1977 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Recaséns - Siches, Luis, 1954-1961 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Reed, Horace, 1964 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Reno, Molly H., 1987 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Ried, Alan, 1987 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Riesenfeld, Alphonse, 1964 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Rittenberg, Louis, 1957 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Robinson, Leonard Wallace, 1943 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Röling, Bert V. A., 1950-1982 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Rogers, Lindsay, 1940-1967 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 42)
  - Rokach, Livia, 1982-1983 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Romoser, George K., 1975 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., Undated (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Rosas, Allan, 1981-1986 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Rosen, Georg (Ambassador), 1959-1960 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Rossides, Zenon (Ambassador), 1977-1978 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Rothschild, Richard C., 1942 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Rubin, Alfred P., 1976-1985 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Rukeyser, Muriel (Redress), 1973-1978 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 46)
  - Russell of Liverpool, Lord, 1959 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 46)
  - S - miscellaneous correspondence, Undated (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Sacharoff, Mark, 1971-1972 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Saidel, Rochelle, 1984 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Sakamoto, Yoshikazu, 1982 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Salmon, Jean, 1972-1982 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Salomon, Albert, 1941 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Sandowsky, Muriel, 1976-1981 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 51)
  - Schaetzler, Bundesminister, 1978 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Schick, Marvin, 1970 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Schönbauer, Elfriede, 1984 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Schoenberg, Harris O., 1965 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Schoenfeld, Thomas, 1985-1987 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Schuman, Frederick L., 1939-1967 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 53)
  - Schwarz, Reta, 1967 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 54)
  - Schwarz, George, 1938 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Schwarzenberger, G., 1955-1964 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Schwarzschild, Steven S., 1974-1979 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Schwebel, Stephen M., 1963-1971 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 56)
  - Schwelb, Egon, 1953-1976 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 56)
  - Schwenck, Hans-Günter, 1970 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 56)
  - Seligman, Eustace, 1954 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 57)
  - Sharp, Walter R., 1945-1954 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 57)
  - Sheldon, James H., 1958 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 57)
  - Shotwell, James T., 1940-1958 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 57)
  - Shumlin, Herman, 1958 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 58)
  - Shuster, George N., 1957 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 58)
  - Simon, Marc, 1968-1969 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 58)
  - Simpson, Thomas Lee, 1968-1977 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 59)
  - Singer, J. David, 1962-1980 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 60)
  - Smirnov, William, 1979 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 61)
  - Smith, Russell F. W., 1958 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 61)
  - Smylie, Robert F., 1979; 1983 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 61)
  - Sohn, Louis B., 1954-1982 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 62)
  - Somerville, John, 1979-1983 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 63)
  - Somerville, John, 1984-1990 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 64)
  - Somit, Albert, 1962-1965 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 65)
  - Sommerich, Otto C., 1954 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 65)
  - Sørensen, Bent, 1957-1978 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 65)
  - Sorensen, Gillian Martin, 1979-1987 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 65)
  - Spain, David, 1974 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 66)
  - Spencer, John H., 1964 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 66)
  - Spero, Sterling, 1945; 1947 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 66)
  - Sprecher, Drexel, 1949-1990 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 66)
  - Srivastava, G.P., 1978 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 67)
  - St. John, Edward, 1990-1991 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 67)
  - Starbuck, Eric, 1943 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 67)
  - Stavins, Ralph, 1976 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 67)
  - Stavropoulos, Constantin A., 1964-1967 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 67)
  - Stegenda, James A., 1977; 1991 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 67)
  - Steinig, Leon, 1951; 1957 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 68)
  - Steiniger, Peter Alfons, 1978-1979 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 68)
  - Steinitz, Hans, 1957 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 68)
  - Stevens, Hope, 1979 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 68)
  - Stoessinger, John G., 1956-1968 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 69)
  - Stonier, Tom, 1969-1972 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 70)
  - Strauss, Leo, 1942 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 70)
  - Stringer, Ann, 1981-1982 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 70)
  - Stuby, Gerhard, 1983-1991 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 71)
  - Sturges, Wesley A., 1950 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 72)
  - Sturmthal, Adolf, 1953 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 72)
  - Sundqvist, Ulf, 1974 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 72)
  - Suter, Keith D., 1986 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 72)
  - Svahnström, Bertil, 1970-1972 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 73)
  - Swerdlow, Amy, 1979 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 73)
  - Swift, Richard N., 1963 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 73)
  - Swing, Sally G., 1959 (Box 7 (7-General correspondence), Folder 73)
  - T, U, V - miscellaneous correspondence, Undated (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Taplinger, Richard, 1969 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Taylor, A.J.P., 1953-1954 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Thomas, Claire Sherman, 1986 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Thorne, John E., 1970 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Toeplitz, Heinrich, 1977 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Tree, Marietta, 1961 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Tung, William L., 1973-1974 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Ulatowska, Lisinka, 1988-1990 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Ulich, Elsa Brandström, 1939 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Van Panhuys, Jonkheer H. F., 1955 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Van Wagenen, Richard W., 1954 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Vance, Cyrus, 1980 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Velasco, Eugenio, 1977-1978 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Verwey, Wil, 1972 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Vincineau, Michel, 1981-1982 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Vollmer, Antje, 1982-1986 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Von Borsig, Tet Arnold, 1965 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 5)
  - W, X, Y, Z - miscellaneous correspondence, Undated (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Wadsworth, James (Ambassador), 1957 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Wald, George, 1969-1975 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Wallach, Sidney, 1940 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Walton, Ernest, 1957 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Warburg, James P., 1954 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Watanabe, Takuro, 1979 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Weiss, Ted (Senator), 1978-1986 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Weisskopf, Victor F., 1956-1985 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Weizsäcker, Ernst U. von, 1983-1984 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Wertheim, Maurice, 1942 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Weston, Burns H., 1967-1990 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Weyl, Roland, 1979-1989 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Whitney, Courtney, 1950 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Whitton, John B., 1939-1953 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Wiener, Alfred, 1951; 1960 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Wilder, Jack, 1976 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Willfort, Margarita, 1951 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Williams, William Appleman, 1983-1984 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Winter, Ernst Karl, 1940 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Witeck, John, 1984-1985 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Wittfogel, Karl, 1940 August (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Wittner, Lawrence S., 1977-1978 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Wolf, Friederica (Fritzi), 1971 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Wolf, Udo, 1987 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Wolf, Victor Jr., 1952 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Wolfers, Arnold, 1951; 1958 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Wolfson, Manfred, 1965 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Wolman, Leo, 1941 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Woodward, Beverly, 1974; 1983 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Wright, Quincy, 1948-1970 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Yamasaki, Tokihiko, 1978 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Young, Andrew (Ambassador), 1977 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Youngblood, Patricia, 1986-1987 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Zeisel, Hans, 1954-1981 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Zeller, Belle, 1948-1979 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Zinn, Howard, 1987-1989 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Zoerb, Richard M., 1962 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Zukmann, Marion, 1965-1981 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Zweig, Konrad & Ann, 1974-1982 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Zwilling, Baron, 1965 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 17)
  - General correspondence re: offprints, Undated (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence with publishers, 7.505 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 19-58)
    - Alethia Press (Howard Friel), 1990 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 19)
    - Alfred A. Knopf, Jr. (Vintage Books), 1957-1958 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 20)
    - American Journal of International Law (Eleanor H. Finch, William W. Bishop), 1954-1982 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 21)
    - The American Political Science Review, 1954-1983 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 22)
    - American Report (Robert S. Lecky), 1972 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 23)
    - AMS Press, 1971-1977 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 24)
    - The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, 1971-1972 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 25)
    - Annual Review of Peace Activism, 1989 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 25)
    - Associated Lawyers Publishing Co., 1959 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 25)
    - Annual Review of UN Affairs, 1954-1956 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 26)
    - Beacon Press (Thomas Bledsoe), 1957 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 27)
    - Bulletin of Peace Proposals (Marek Thee), 1977-1982 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 28)
    - The Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1973-1982 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 29)
    - Bulletin of the Peace Studies Institute, 1980 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 29)
    - Canadian Consumer, 1982-1983 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 30)
    - Christianity and Crisis, 1984 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 30)
    - The Churchman (Edna Ruth Johnson), 1978-1990 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 31)
    - P. F. Collier & Son Incorporated (Collier's Yearbook), 1954-1960 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 32)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System, 1944 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 33)
    - Denver Journal of International Law and Policy, 1985 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 34)
    - The Economist, 1978 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 34)
    - The Encyclopedia Americana, 1955-1974 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 35)
    - Encyclopedia of Peace (Institute of International Peace Studies, South Korea), 1984 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 36)
    - Encyclopedia of Social Science, 1961 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 36)
    - Encyclopedia International, 1967-1977 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 36)
    - Encyclopedia Picturama, Inc., 1955 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 36)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1942 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 37)
    - Foreign Policy, 1972 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 37)
    - Freiheit für Oesterreich, 1942-1943 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 37)
    - Funk & Wagnalls Encyclopedia, 1949-1958 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 37)
    - GATT Secretariat, 1959 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 37)
    - Grolier Incorporated, 1961-1977 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 38)
    - Guardian, 1968 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 39)
    - Harper's Magazine, 1942-1978 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 39)
    - The Humanist, 1982 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 39)
    - Indian Journal of International Law (M.K. Nawaz), 1975 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 39)
    - Indochina Today, 1974 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 39)
    - Infantry Journal, 1942 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 40)
    - International Political Science Abstracts, 1972-1973 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 40)
    - International Studies Quarterly, 1982 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 40)
    - Jag Journal, 1977 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 40)
    - Jewish Encyclopedia, 1957 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 41)
    - kontakt, 1975 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 41)
    - The Macmillan Company, 1942-1986 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 41)
    - La Monda Lingvo - Problemo (Richard E. Wood), 1976 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 42)
    - Monograph Series in World Affairs (Univ. of Denver), 1983 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 42)
    - The Nation, 1943-1986 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 43)
    - Neue Justiz, 1987-1988 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 44)
    - New Perspectives, 1977 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 44)
    - The New Republic, 1940 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 44)
    - New Society (Paul Barker), 1973-1974 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 44)
    - The New York Times and The New York Review of Books, 1962-1984 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 45)
    - New York University Press, 1955-1959 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 46)
    - The New Yorker, 1957 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 47)
    - Oceana Publications, 1957 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 48)
    - On Guard, 1988 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 48)
    - Pace Yearbook of International Law, 1989-1990 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 48)
    - Peace and Change, 1981-1988 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 48)
    - Philosophy and Social Criticism, 1988-1989 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 49)
    - Political Science Quarterly, 1946-1951 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 49)
    - Presidential Studies Quarterly (R. Gordon Hoxie), 1978 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 49)
    - Princeton University Press, 1953 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 49)
    - The Progressive, 1967-1983 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 49)
    - Random House, 1962-1971 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 50)
    - Revue Belge de Droit International, 1981 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 51)
    - Rights, 1978 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 51)
    - Sane World, 1962-1983 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 51)
    - Saturday Review, 1964 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 51)
    - Schenkman Publishing Co. (Alfred Schenkman), 1967-1968 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 51)
    - Science and Public Affairs, 1973 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 51)
    - Simon & Schuster, 1951 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 51)
    - Simon Wiesenthal Center, 1985-1989 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 52)
    - SIPRI Yearbook, 1983-1984 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 53)
    - Social Research, 1960 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 54)
    - St. Louis Dispatch, 1987 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 54)
    - Texas International Law Journal, 1975-1978 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 54)
    - Tikkun, 1987 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 55)
    - Time Magazine, 1943 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 55)
    - Twice A Year, 1941 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 55)
    - The Universal Jewish Encyclopedia, 1959 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 55)